Nathan Poulson

Sandy, UT | C: (801)-842-9205 | E: nathan7418@gmail.com

Summary

I am a husband and a father of two awesome boys. I received my associates of Science degree from Dixie State University studying generals. Currently I work at a cabinet shop cutting molding. I have done this for almost four years. It is fun and a great skill to have. One class I took during my final semester at Dixie was Web Development class. I learned basic HTML and CSS during that and I found I really enjoyed it! After that class I practiced HTML and CSS to improve my skill and learn more. I finished a coding boot camp class through the University of Utah in April of 2020. That course was a great learning experience and I continue to try and expand on that knowledge.

Skills

- Quality Assurance
- Organized
- Cash Handling Accuracy
- Dependable and Reliable
- Cheerful and Energetic
- Detail-Oriented
- Computer Savvy
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Nodejs, MySQL, MongoDB, and React

Experience

PRODUCTION WORKER | 05/2019 to Current

Mountain Crest Cabnets - West Jordan, UT

- Cut molding with a variety of different tools
- Put edges on molding with router bits
- Helped on custom jobs with hoods, frames, floating shelves, or adjustable shelves
- Occasionally went out on deliveries

ASSEMBLY WORKER | 08/2016 to 02/2019

Wilding Wallbeds - St. George, UT

- Used hand and power tools to assemble products
- Worked at fast and steady pace to meet production goals
- · Assessed work for errors or compliance issues and made corrections and modifications when necessary
- Read tape measures, drawings, diagrams and specifications for correct assembly
- Kept workstation organized and orderly, making sure production parts, tools, test equipment and documentation were properly stored and maintained
- Worked closely with supervisors and designers to understand and meet production specifications
- Assisted new employees with assembly tasks to maintain production levels
- I was the supervisors 2nd hand man, in charge of supervisor tasks when the leader was absent. This included checking quality work of co-workers, and help train new employees

TEAM LEADER | 04/2015 to 07/2016

Papa Murphy's - South Jordan, UT

- Make Pizzas
- Made sure employees were doing jobs correctly
- Helped train new employees
- Ran the shift when no manager was scheduled
- Customer service/Dealing with angry customers
- Nightly paperwork

• Closed registers, counted money, made sure the store was poperly closed for the night

Education

Copper Hills High School - West Jordan, UT | High School Diploma 07/2016

Dixie State University - St. George, UT | Associates of Science General Studies, 12/2018

University of Utah - Salt Lake City, UT | Coding Bootcamp
Full Stack Programming, 04/2020